http://www.canoescotland.com/privacy

MEMBERSHIP
WHY JOIN?
ADVANCED CANOE WHITE WATER LEADER
ADVANCED SEA KAYAK LEADER (TIDAL & NON-TIDAL)
PADDLESPORT TOURING LEADER
SEA KAYAK LEADER (TIDAL & NON-TIDAL)
Website Privacy Policy
Scottish Canoe Association is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Scottish Canoe Association Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Scottish Canoe Association website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Please Note: The privacy notice below relates to the use of the Scottish Canoe Association website. For the full organisation Privacy Notice (updated April 2018) please read the separate SCA Privacy Notice
COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION Scottish Canoe Association collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Scottish Canoe Association also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your postcode, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Scottish Canoe Association. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Scottish Canoe Association for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Scottish Canoe Association Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Scottish Canoe Association public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.Note:
Scottish Canoe Association does not read any of your private online communications.Scottish Canoe Association encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Scottish Canoe Association so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Scottish Canoe Association is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Scottish Canoe Association and Scottish Canoe Association family of Web sites.
USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION Scottish Canoe Association collects and uses your personal information to operate the Scottish Canoe Association Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Scottish Canoe Association also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Scottish Canoe Association and its affiliates. Scottish Canoe Association may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Scottish Canoe Association does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Scottish Canoe Association may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Scottish Canoe Association may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Scottish Canoe Association, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Scottish Canoe Association does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Scottish Canoe Association keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Scottish Canoe Association, in order to determine what Scottish Canoe Association services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customised content and advertising within Scottish Canoe Association to customers whose behaviour indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Scottish Canoe Association Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Scottish Canoe Association or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Scottish Canoe Association; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Scottish Canoe Association, or the public.
USE OF COOKIES The Scottish Canoe Association Web site use "cookies" to help you personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise Scottish Canoe Association pages, or register with Scottish Canoe Association site or services, a cookie helps Scottish Canoe Association to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Scottish Canoe Association Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Scottish Canoe Association features that you customised.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Scottish Canoe Association services or Web sites you visit.
SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION Scottish Canoe Association secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. Scottish Canoe Association secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT Scottish Canoe Association will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Scottish Canoe Association encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Scottish Canoe Association is protecting your information.
CONTACT INFORMATION Scottish Canoe Association welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Scottish Canoe Association has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Scottish Canoe Association at webmaster@canoescotland.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
OUR
PARTNERS
QUICKLINKS JOIN NOWGO PADDLINGFIND A CLUBBRITISH CANOEINGPOLICIESCONTACT US
LEGAL PRIVACY POLICYCOOKIE POLICYTERMS OF USEACCESSIBILITYSITEMAPLOGIN
© 2020
Copyright Scotland Canoe Association. All Rights Reserved.
Website designed by
Website Sorted Bristol web design
Share by:
